David López López

Madrid, Spain 14 May 2001

 d.3lopm@gmail.com

(+34) 695 612 581

Driving License B

LINKEDIN / PORTFOLIO

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native English B2

KNOWLEDGE

Unity

Unreal Engine 5

C/C++/C#

Python

Java

Javascript

DaVinci Resolve

Adobe Premiere

Adobe After Effects

Offi ce

Agile Development

INTERESTS

Software & Videogame Development

AI AR

VR

Video Edition

Teamwork

I am a videogame and software developer with a passion for bringing ideas to life through games and applications.

I have worked on diverse projects as a programmer and leading agile development teams.

My comfort zone lies in developing Unity games with C#, but I am interested in Unreal Engine as a development engine. Additionally, I have developed applications using JavaScript and implemented artificial intelligence using Python and C# for some of my projects.

Other than that, I have done projects related to web and mobile apps.

EDUCATION

2023	42 Madrid piscine	42 Madrid
2023	"Experto en Shader Graph Unity" Course	Udemy
2019-2023	Degree in Video Game Design and Development	Rey Juan Carlos University
2021	Unity Course	Udemy

EXPERIENCE

PRESENT	Lead Programmer	Mental Gaming
2023	Feed Yourself App - Programmer & Scrum Master	Team Chubby Cat
2023	CyberHell - Gameplay Programmer & Scrum Master	Team Chubby Cat
2022-2023	Chess: Holy War - Gameplay Programmer & Scrum Master	Team Chubby Cat
2017 . D	0	
2017 - Present	Own projects	Freelance